Finding Aid for the Aron Kuppermann Papers 1946-2012
Caltech Archives
- World Bank 1983- 2005, Series 2.
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil 1992
  - Correspondence and support material I, April-July 1992 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and support material II, August-November 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Travel related documents, August 1992-February 1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Meetings notes, August 15-21, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Supervision mission Science Research and Training Project PADCT II: Aide memoire, September 1, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Supervision report: Science Research and Training Project Loan 3269-BR, November 18, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico 1993
  - Correspondence and support material, December 1992-August 1993 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Travel related documents, February-March 1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Meetings notes, February 21-27, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil: April-May 1993
  - Correspondence and support material, January-May 1993 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Travel related documents, March-May 1993 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Meetings notes, April 1993 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - PADCT I: Evaluative data final report, April 1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Supervision mission Science Research and Training Project PADCT II: Aide memoire, April 16-20, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil: October 1993
  - Correspondence, September 1993-January 1994 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Brazil Mission: Reference material, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Limited supervision mission Science Research and Training Project PADCT II: Aide memoire, January 8, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - World Bank Mission to China 1994
  - China Key Studies Development Project: Correspondence and support material, December 1993-January 1994 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Travel related documents, December 1993-July 1994 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Meetings notes, January 1994 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Mid-Term review report: China Key Studies Development Project (Cr. 2210-CHA), January 25, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil: January-February 1994
  - Travel related documents, February 1994 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and support material, March-June 1994 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - World Bank Mission to Argentina 1994
  - Correspondence and support material, May-August 1994 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Travel related documents, July-September 1994 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil: June 1994
  - Correspondence and support material, March-September 1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Travel related documents, May-November 1994 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Project completion report on Brazil Science and Technology Project (Loan 2489-BR), June 14, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Limited supervision mission Science Research and Training Project PADCT II: Aide memoire, June 15, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico 1994
  - Correspondence and support material, July-December 1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Travel related documents, December 1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil 1995
  - Correspondence, May-June 1995 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Travel related documents, May-December 1995 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Meetings notes, June 1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico 1997
  - Correspondence and support material, January-April 1997 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Travel related documents, January-November 1997 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Meetings notes, February 1997 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil: March 1997
  - Correspondence and support material, February-April 1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Project Concept Document (PCD) group meeting correspondence, February-March 1997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Meeting held in Washinton, D.C. on February 27, 1997.
  - Travel related documents, March 1997 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil: April-May 1997
  - Travel related documents, April-May 1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and support material, April-July 1997 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - World Bank Mission to China 1997
  - Correspondence and support material, May-June 1997 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Travel related documents, November 1997 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico 1998
  - Correspondence and support material, February-April 1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Travel related documents, March-December 1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Mexico Science and Technology Project: Aide memoire, April 22, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Meetings notes, April 22, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil: April-May 1998
  - Correspondence and support material, November 1997-February 1998 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Travel related documents, April 1998 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - World Bank Mission to Chile: September 1998
  - Correspondence, June 1998-June 1999 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Travel related documents, September 1998-November 1999 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil: November-December 1998
  - Support Program for Scientific and Technological Development (PADCT III): Reference material, November 1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    In Portuguese.
  - Travel related documents, November 1999 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico 1999
  - Correspondence and support material, March-May 1999 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Travel related documents, June 1999 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico 2000
  - Correspondence and support material, June-July 2000 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Travel related documents, July 2000 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - World Bank Mission to Uganda 2003-2005
  - Travel related documents, December 2003-April 2005 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Meetings notes, March 2005 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and support material, March 2005 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Project report: Uganda Millenium Science Intiative, September 2005 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- California Institute of Technology, Series 3.
  - Division of Chemistry and Chemical Engineering, Subseries 1.
    - Division Committees
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Computing Needs of the Division, 1978-1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Chemical Graduate Study Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Chemical Graduate Study Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Chemical Physics Faculty Search Committee, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Chemical Physics Seminar (CPS) Organizing Committee, Correspondence and related material, 1992, 1994-1999, 2000-2009 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Chemical Physics Seminar (CPS), 1987-1990 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Chemical Physics Seminar (CPS), 1991-1992, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Chemical Physics Seminar (CPS), 1996-1998 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Chemical Physics Seminar (CPS), 1999-2003 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Chemical Physics Seminar (CPS), 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Chemical Physics Seminar (CPS), 2006-2008 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Chemical Physics Seminar (CPS), 2009-2010 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Chemistry Division Computing Committee, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Chemistry Division Computing Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Curriculum and Undergraduate Studies Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Staffing and Long Range Planning Committee, 1973-1977, 1991-1997, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Closed file.
    - Division, Administrative Matters and miscellaneous
    - Graduate course in physical chemistry, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Post doctoral candidates, 1969-1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Post doctoral candidates, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Post doctoral candidates, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Post doctoral candidates, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Letters of recommendation, 1957-1970 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Nomination of Prof. Rudolph A. Marcus for the Nobel Prize for Chemistry, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Division general correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Division general correspondence, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Division general correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Division general correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Division general correspondence, 1996-1998, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Division Faculty meetings, 1989-1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Division Faculty meetings, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Division Faculty meetings, 1998-2001, 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Institute Business, Subseries 2.
    - Institute Committees
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure Committee, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Committee on Supercomputers (ACS), 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Committee on Supercomputers (ACS), 1987 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Benefits Committee, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Caltech Campus Organization Committee, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Exchange Programs and Study Abroad (CEPSA), 2006 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Computing Advisory Committee (CAC), 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Computing Advisory Committee (CAC), 1991-1994 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Computing Advisory Committee (CAC), 1996, 1998-1999, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Management Committee (FMC) of the Caltech Concurrent Supercomputing Facilities (CCSF), 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Nominating Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Board Steering Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Feynmann Theory Center Committee, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Students and Scholars Committee, 1987-1991 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Institute Programs Committee (IPC), 1985-1986, 1988-1991, 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Membership and Bylaws Committee, 2001-2003 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Scholarships and Financial Aid Committee (SFAC), 1988-1992 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Scholarships and Financial Aid Committee (SFAC), 1993-1995 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Scholarships and Financial Aid Committee (SFAC), 1996-2000 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Scholarships and Financial Aid Committee (SFAC), 2001-2003 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Scholarships and Financial Aid Committee (SFAC), 2006-2009 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Institute, miscellaneous
    - "An analysis of tenure granting policies", March 1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - System development Foundation Board of Trustees visit, 12 December 1983 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Includes talk overheads.
    - Institute matters, correspondence, 1984, 1989, 1993, 1997-1999 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Distinguished Alumni Award nomination of Professor George C. Schatz, 2005-2007 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Distinguished Alumni Award nomination of Professor Donald G. Truhlar, 2006-2007 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Teaching, Series 4.
  - University of Illinois 1955-1963, Subseries 1.
    - Physical chemistry placement exams, 1955-1959 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry 240: Course outline and exams, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Chemistry 245-246: Course outline, exams and lecture notes, 1955-1959 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Chemistry 342: Course outline, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Chemistry 344: Exams, 1956-1958 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Chemistry 345: Experiment instructions, 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Chemistry 347: Experiment handouts, 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Chemistry 394: Exams, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Chemistry 442: Course outline and exams, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Chemistry 445: Seminar schedule, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Chemistry 446: Exams and problem sets, 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Chemistry 446: Lectures notes, 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Chemistry 447: Exams and lecture notes, 1961-1963 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry 448: Exams and lecture notes, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - California Institute of Technology 1970-2010, Subseries 2.
    - Caltech teaching 1970-1979
    - Chemistry 1: Course outline, exams and lecture notes, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Chemistry 26: Experiment instructions and handouts, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, problem set solutions and exams, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Chemistry 135: Lecture notes, exams and problem sets, 1970-1971, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Chemistry 227: Course outline and lecture notes, 1970-1972 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry 227: Lecture notes, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Chemistry 227: Lecture notes I, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Chemistry 227: Lecture notes II, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Caltech teaching 1980-1989
    - Chemistry 125: Problem sets, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline and problem sets, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline and problem sets, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Chemistry 125: Problem sets and exams, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Chemistry 125: Problem sets and exams, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline and problem sets, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Chemistry 227: Lecture notes, 1983, 1986, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Caltech teaching 1990-1999
    - Chemistry 21: Course outline, lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Chemistry 125: Problem sets and exams, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Chemistry 135: Course outline, lecture notes and problem sets, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Chemistry 135: Lecture notes and problem sets, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Chemistry 135: Course outline, lecture notes and problem sets, 1996-1998 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Chemistry 227: Lecture notes, 1993-1994, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Caltech teaching 2000-2010
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, lecture notes, problem sets and exams, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry 125: Course outline, problem sets and exams, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Chemistry 125: Lecture notes, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Chemistry 135: Course outline and problem sets, 2000-2002 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry 135: Course outline, lecture notes and problem sets, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Chemistry 135: Course outline, lecture notes and problem sets, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Chemistry 135: Course outline and lecture notes, 2008-2009 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Chemistry 227: Course outline and lecture notes, 2003, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Chemistry 227: Lecture notes, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Writings and Publications, Series 5.
  - Manuscripts, Subseries 1.
    - "Determina?ão de carga de flambagem", 1940's (Box 43, Folder 1)
      In Potuguese.
    - "Laboratóries de química analitica", 1946 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - "Apontamentos de matemática para os exames vestibulares", 1948 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      2 copies of first edition in Potuguese.
    - "Sobre o campo magnético criado por corrente elétrica", 1948 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - "Cálculo da média geométrica na determina?ão de masses pelo método da dupla pesagem de Gauss", 1950 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - "The Dirac vector Model", 1958 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - "Dimensionality in physical chemistry", 1959 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - "Calculations on the unimolecular decomposition of energized molecules", 1961 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - "Kinetics of thermal isomerization of methylcyclopropane", 1962 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - "Relation between threshold energy, rate constant and reaction cross section", 1965 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Physical Chemistry manuscript 1968
      Lecture notes of a class taught by A. Kuppermann and R.E. Dickerson that were transcribed in order to publish them as a textbook by W.A. Benjamin, Inc.
    - Correspondence with W.A. Benjamin related to Physical Chemistry manuscript, 1964-1966 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with W.A. Benjamin related to Physical Chemistry manuscript, 1967-1970 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Lecture notes and transcripts, January 1966-May 1967 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Lecture notes and transcripts, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript chapters 1-2, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript chapters 3-4, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript chapters 5-6, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - "An analysis of tenure granting policies" 1977(See: Series 3, subseries 2, Institute business)
    - "Anisotropic intermolecular potentials for He+CO2, He+CS2, and He+OCS from crossed beam scattering experiments", 1988 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - "Sensitivity analysis of the differential scattering cross section to the He+CO2 interaction potential", 1990 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - "An Electron impact spectroscopy investigation od diketene", 1992 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Analysis of paper by Y. Ohrn and J. Linderberg entitled "Hyperspherical coordinates in four particle systems", 1992 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Reviews of manuscripts and proposals of others
    - Reviews, 1961-1964 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Reviews, 1965-1967 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Reviews, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Reviews, 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Reviews, 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Reviews, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Reviews, 1986-1995 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Reviews, 1996-1999 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Reviews, 2002-2008 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Reprints, Subseries 2.
    - Reprints by Aron Kuppermann
    - "Curso de geométria analítica", 1948 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      Copy of first edition in Potuguese.
    - "Estudo da Formula dos Hidrocarbonetos", 1948 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      3 copies.
    - "Apontamentos de matemática para os exames vestibulares", 1949 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      Copy of second edition in Potuguese.
    - "Contribucao ao estudo do Paracoro de ciclos", 1949 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      2 copies.
    - "Curso de geométria analítica", 1950 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - "Exercícios resolvidos de Álgebra", 1951 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - "Sobre a definicao e a determinacao do numero de constituintes independentes de um sistema"; "Do uso da media aritmetica na determinacao de massas pelo metodo da dupla pesagem de Gauss", 1951 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - "Summary of proceedings of an informal discussion on the radiation chemistry of water", 1953 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - "Quantum-mechanical calculation of one-electron properties: General formulation", 1958 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - "The quantum-mechanical calculation of one-electron properties: One- and two-center moment integrals"", 1959 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - "Decomposition of n-Butane in an electric discharge", 1959 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - "Theoretical foundations of radiation chemistry", 1959 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - "Ferrous and ceris sulfate dosimeters", 1960 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - "Nonmolecular nature of the nitric-oxide thermal decomposition of n-Butane", 1960 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - "Fundamentos da química: teoria", 1960 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - "Diffusion kineticks in radiation chemistry", 1961 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - "Diffusion kinetics", 1961 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - "Ion molecule reactions in the nitrogen-deutrium system", 1961 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - "Diffusion kinetick in radiation chemistry, Part I", 1962 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - "Diffusion kinetick in radiation chemistry, Part II", 1962 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - "Application of numerical methods to the theory of the periodic deviations in the Schotty effect", 1962 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - "Determination of electronic energy levels of molecules by low energy electron impact spectroscopy", 1962 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - "Differences between low energy electron impact ? at large scattering angle", 1963 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - "Electron impact spectroscopy", 1963 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - "Excited states produced by low energy electrons", 1964 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - "Radiation chemistry", 1965 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - "Energy threshold", 1966 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - "Diffusion model of the radiation chemistry of Aqueous solutions", 1967 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - "Electron impact excitation cross section for the two lowest triplet states of molecular hydrogen", 1967 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - "Dynamics of reaction of monoenergetic atoms in a thermal gas", 1967 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - "Reaction of monoenergetic deuterium atoms with hydrogen molecules", 1967 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - "Argon resonance line lamp for vacuum ultraviolet photochemistry", 1968 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - "Difference in the angular dependencies ? by low energy electron impact spectroscopy", 1968 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - "Chemical reaction cross sections and rate constants", 1968 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - "Vibrational energy transfer in collisions between diatomic molecules", 1968 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - "Formation of positive and negative ions on rhenium ? and thoriated tungsten surfaces", 1968 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - "Triplet states of acetylene by electron impact", 1968 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - "Rearrangement collisions", 1968 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - "A low-energy, high-resolution electron impact spectrometer", 1968 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - "Angular dependence of low energy electron impact excitation cross section ?", 1969 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - "Low-energy, high-angle electron impact spectrometer", 1969 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - "Applications of the statistical phase space theory to reactions of atomic hydrogen with deuterium halides", 1969 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - "Instrumental effects in retarding field energy analyzer", 1969 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - "Reactive collisions", 1969 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - "Differential and integral cross sections for excitation ? by electron impact", 1970 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - "Electron impact spectrometry", 1970 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Copy of the reprint.
    - "Differential elastic scattering", 1970 (Box 49, Folder 5)